

TAJNUR RAHMAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Java|Spring boot|Angular

+ +880 1312 136602

tajnur779@gmail.com

#197 Senpara Parbata, Mirpur-10, Dhaka 1216

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To develop my career in IT fields as a Software Developer based on JAVA specializing in Spring Boot back-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for Dynamic Web Applications. Well-versed in Java JDK, Spring boot, Hibernate, RESTful API, Angular, Oracle Database, MySQL, Bootstrap, JasperReports, Unified Modeling Language (UML), Git, and Trello. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

Daffodil International (DIPTI) IsDB-BISEW

Enterprise Systems Analysis and Design-JEE

Diploma in Software Development (JEE)

2022 - 2023 2020 - 2021

EXPERTISE

- Java EE/ J2EE
- Spring Boot
- Oracle Database
- RESTful API
- Angular
- Flutter
- Git
- Selenium

PROJECTS

Garment Management System

Technology : Spring Boot, RESTful API, Mysql DB,

Angular, Bootstrap

: Employee Management, Order Handling, **Features**

Production line Control, Accounting, Report

Role : Team Member

: https://github.com/tajnurR/SpringBoot Git

https://github.com/tajnurR/Angular

Email Tester - Digital Marketing Tools

Technology : Spring Boot, RESTful API, Mysql DB,

WebSocket, Thymeleaf, Bootstrap

Features : Verify any Email, Find Email By Name and

company, Bulk Email Verify

Role : Individual

Git : https://github.com/tajnurR/ProEmailVerifyer

Pharmacy POS

Technology Core Java, Swing, Mysql DB

Inventory, Sales point, User Role, Dynamic **Features**

Dashboard, Report Making

Role Individual

https://github.com/tajnurR/Pharmacy-sales-pos Git

EXPERIENCE

Freelancing - Web Scraping

Fiverr & xfluence.io

2020 - Present

Last 2 year I'm working with Selenium WebDriver Web automation sector. Trying to build my freelancing career in Web Scraping. Where I successfully completed 200+ projects in selenium WebDriver with Java 8, 11, and

Digital Marketing Trainer

IBCS-PRIMAX Software (Bangladesh) Ltd.

2020 - 2021

As a digital marketing trainer, my responsibility is to train new cammer students about training marketing technic. Make them skillful and launch them in the freelancing marketplace. And had to Provide support and instruction to build their freelancing career.

EDUCATION

Govt. Azizul Haque College, Bogura

BSS in Economic

2015 - 2019

CGPA:2.97 out of 4

APBn School & College Bogura

2012 - 2014

GPA:5 out of 5

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Father's Name Abdul Based PK

Mother's Name Mst Nurjahan Begom Date of Birth September 10, 1997

Marital Status Unmarried

Religion Islam

Shakhahaer, Shakhahaer Kahaloo, **Permanent Address**

Kahalu, Kahalu, Bogura 5880

REFERENCES:

Reference: 01 Reference: 02

Name : Md. Moshaidul Islam

Organization : IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship IsDB-BISEW IT Scholarship

Designation : Consultant Mobile : 01711071219

E-Mail : moshaidul@gmail.com

: Academic Relation

Muhammad Emran Hossain

Instructor of Java Enterprise Edition

01619192323

emranhss@gmail.com

Academic

DECLARATION:

I do hereby state that the above information is true and authentic to the best of my knowledge.

Md Tajnur Rahman

Signature Date: 03-03-23